<movie>


	<movieInfo>
		<name>Premam</name>
		<Dname>Alphonse Puthren</Dname>
		<cast>Nivin Pauly, Sai Pallavi, Anupama, Medonna</cast>
		<releaseDate>29th May 2015</releaseDate>
		<category>Malayalam</category>
		<genre>Comedy,Drama,Romance</genre>
		<imdb>8.3</imdb>
		<image>Photo/premam.jpg</image>
		<description>There are not too many films that we have seen during recent years, which can keep you entertained from start to finish, like Alphonse Puthren’s Premam.

The film follows the life of its protagonist George David (Nivin Pauly), right from his teenage years as he starts his romantic journey. It all begins, as he is seen desperately wooing the local beauty, Mary George (Anupama Parameswaran). The escapades continue in a mostly hilarious tone and in an engaging manner.

With some genuinely relatable performances from a bunch of fresh faces, the film rarely gives you time to get distracted. It’s no mean achievement in a film, which goes on for more than 160 minutes.

Alphonse Puthren, who made a well-appreciated debut with Neram, is in top form as he displays his signature with funny episodes strewn to each other in a competent manner. That is never easy considering he is narrating a simple storyline that has barely enough drama or those breathtaking twists, like it is a custom here.

The camera by Anend C Chandran and the music by Rajesh Murugesan include the highlights of the film.

But the major concern is the film’s duration. The overindulgence of the makers, as they fall completely in love with their own style, is definitely seen. As they go on with their obsession to continue with their narration, the viewers’ interests seem to have been given a lesser priority. Still, that doesn’t take away the merits of this laugh riot.

Among the heroines, it is Sai Pallavi (playing Malar) who steals the show with her energy and confidence. In fact quite a number of fresh faces make you laugh with smart lines and their natural behavior during humorous situations. Among the more experienced actors, Soubeen Shaheer, Vinay Fort and Renji Panicker need special mention for their spectacular show in brief but effective roles.

But then, the whole film is about around fifteen years in the life of George David and Nivin Pauly comes up with a stellar show. He has given his heart and soul to the role, performing the transformations of his character quite remarkably. Take a bow, hero!

We can go on and on about the details, but it’s better to enjoy the fun at the cinemas, without divulging more about what’s in store.

Premam is all for some genuine fun and perhaps, a few nostalgic moments as well. It’s a lengthy ride for sure, but it will leave you wanting for more. Grab a box of popcorn and watch this one pronto!</description>
	</movieInfo>
	
	<movieInfo>
		<name>Arjun Reddy</name>
		<Dname>Sandeep Reddy Vanga</Dname>
		<cast>Vijay Deverkonda, Shalini Pandey</cast>
		<releaseDate>25th Auguest 2017</releaseDate>
		<category>Telegu</category>
		<genre>Romance,Action</genre>
		<imdb>8.1</imdb>
		<image>Photo/arjunreddy.jpg</image>
		<description>Arjun Reddy Deshmukh is a house surgeon at St. Mary's Medical College in Mangalore, India. Despite being a brilliant student, he has severe anger management problems that earn the wrath of the dean of the college. Arjun's aggressive nature also earns him a reputation among his juniors as a college bully. After having a brawl alongside his friend Kamal against members of the opposing team during an inter-college football match the dean asks Arjun to either apologise or leave the college. Arjun initially chooses to leave the college, but stays back after meeting first-year student Preethi Shetty.

Arjun and his friend Shiva enter a third-year classroom and announce that Arjun is in love with Preethi and asserts that she is exclusive to him. Initially afraid, Preethi starts adjusting herself to Arjun's overbearing attitude. She eventually reciprocates his feelings and they develop an intimate relationship. Arjun graduates with an MBBS degree and leaves for Mussoorie to pursue a Master's degree in Orthopedic surgery. Over the course of three years, Arjun's and Preethi's relationship becomes stronger. Months later, Arjun visits Preethi's house, where her father sees them kissing and throws Arjun out.

Preethi's father opposes her and Arjun's relationship due to Arjun's brash behaviour and also because they belong to different castes. Arjun demands that Preethi must make a decision within six hours otherwise he will end their relationship. Following this incident, Preethi's parents seize her phone, making her unable to contact Arjun. By the time she manages to visit Arjun's house, he is drunk, injects morphine into himself, and becomes unconscious for two days. Preethi is then forcibly married to someone from her caste. Arjun learns about the marriage from Shiva and goes to her house in protest. He is assaulted and gets arrested for making a scene. Arjun's father ostracises him from the family home for damaging his reputation.

With Shiva's help, Arjun finds a rented flat and joins a private hospital as a surgeon. To cope with his emotions, he starts taking drugs, attempts one-night stands, buys a pet dog and names it after Preethi and drinks alcohol; all of which are unsuccessful. Within months, he becomes a successful surgeon and a high-functioning alcoholic who is feared by the hospital's staff members, one of the reasons being his high surgery count. Arjun's self-destructing behaviour and refusal to move on worries Shiva and Kamal. He persuades one of his patients, Jia Sharma, a leading film star, to have a no-strings relationship with him, which he ends when she falls in love with him.

On a day off, Arjun unwillingly agrees to perform a life-saving surgery and collapses with dehydration. The hospital staff examine his blood samples, which show traces of alcohol and cocaine. The hospital chief files a case against Arjun, who accepts the truth on the grounds of violating his professional ethics during an in-house court hearing, despite Shiva making arrangements to bail him out. Arjun's medical license is cancelled for five years and he is evicted from the flat. The next morning, Shiva manages to reach Arjun to convey his grandmother's death; he meets his father, and they reconcile. Arjun gives up his self-destructive habits soon after.

While leaving for a vacation, Arjun sees a pregnant Preethi sitting in a park. Convinced that she is unhappy with her marriage, Arjun meets her after returning from his vacation. Preethi reveals that she left her husband days after their marriage and continued to work in a clinic. She tells Arjun that he is the child's father, and they reunite. The pair marries, and Preethi's father apologises for misunderstanding their love for each other.</description>
	</movieInfo>
	
	<movieInfo>
		<name>Be With You</name>
		<Dname>Le Jung-Hoon</Dname>
		<cast>Son Ye-Jin, So Ji-Sub, </cast>
		<releaseDate>14th March 2018</releaseDate>
		<category>Korean</category>
		<genre>Drama,Fantasy,Romance</genre>
		<imdb>7.7</imdb>
		<image>Photo/bewithyou.jpg</image>
		<description>This is a wondrous little film, if a bit confusing. The summary is simple: a woman re-appears a year after her death without memory of her husband and child, who are the first to find her sitting alone  near a railroad track. The movie unfolds to  reveal the entire story and is well worth watching .


To be enjoyed here are the actors , who do very good jobs of portraying their parts. Cliché? Hardly . the story is unique , the characters well- portrayed . the “penguin” scene is quit humorous . a perfect film?  No  . But it’s a cut above typical love stories.  Does it fall short  in spots and leave the user scratching one’s head at times ? yes but it  also brings laughter ,appreciation , one significantly unexpected “wince” moment  and a few tears. It is unfortunate that some are so jaded and demanding in their film watching that they can no longer enjoy a simple bit of story– telling.


For the romantics, for those who enjoy a decent story (if a bit odd) , for  those who appreciate a twist  or two during the recounting of events, this is a quite a nice experience . you may have to watch the ending twice to get the all-too-quick plot twist , but it’s easy enough to hit replay. All in all, worth watching.
</description>
	</movieInfo>
	
	<movieInfo>
		<name>More Than blue</name>
		<Dname>Tae-Yeon Won</Dname>
		<cast> Sang-Woo Kwon, Bo-young Lee, Beom-su Lee</cast>
		<releaseDate>11th March 2009</releaseDate>
		<category>Korean</category>
		<genre>Drama,Romance</genre>
		<imdb>7.6</imdb>
		<image>Photo/morethanblue.jpg</image>
		<description>K and Cream first meet each other in high school and both are orphans; K was abandoned by his mother after his father died of cancer who nevertheless left him a sizeable sum of money, while Cream lost her entire family in a car accident. The two become soulmates and come to share a home. Knowing that Cream's biggest fear is to be left alone, K keeps the fact that he has terminal cancer a secret, and instead he urges her to marry a kind and healthy man. When Cream announces that she is in love with affluent doctor Joo-hwan, K is left heartbroken, but is satisfied that she has met her ideal partner.

Believing Cream has really found someone she loves, K asked Joo-hwan's fiancée to break up with him. Joo-hwan's fiancée agrees under the condition that K lets her take photographs of him for her exhibit about death. It is later revealed that Cream first learned about K's illness when she rummaged through his belongings to find what men liked for her new song, but in fact turned out to be pain medication for terminal cancer patients. Earlier in the movie, Cream asked K what his wish was. It was for Cream to find a good and healthy man to spend her life with. With her knowledge of his illness, Cream thus faked falling in love with Joo-hwan, in order to appease K. This perspective of Cream's is revealed toward the end of the movie.

In the end, Cream apologizes to Joo-hwan for cheating him and finds K and lives with him till he died. Joo-hwan then visits their grave, implying Cream committed suicide after K's death.
</description>
	</movieInfo>


</movie>
